Shahrukh Ahmed

Web Developer

About

I have been building websites for 3 years now. Most have been personal projects (links in the website) to get an educational website up and going. After giving it a shot, I am back in the job-market and I want to give webdevelopment as a career a go. It's a field that I find myself excited about because of the avenues available to learn, experiment and build something worthwhile. And I hope to do it in a professional capacity in the near future.

Contact













Skills

- HTML CSS3
- CSS3 JavaScript
- DjangoVue.js
- D3.js Bootstrap
- JquerySVG
- React.js

Work Experience

Freelance Web Development

August 2018 - current

Took up an initial project that involved revamping the client's website. Later on requirement evolved to creating 7 websites (duescta.com) for the client's institution, which included various schools and colleges.

- Created multiple UI wireframes.
- Django based CRUD app. A few tweaks to the Django Admin system and backend was dynamic enough to add and remove information relating to admissions, news and other updates.

Freelance Writing

July 2015 - current

I have freelanced for local and international clients. I have written about current-affairs, healthcare, history, entertainment but the bulk of my work has been writing about Climate Change and renewable energy sources. My work typically involves going through dozens of research papers and writing an article that makes a topic easy and clear for the readers to grasp.

Yahoo!

August 2014 - June 2015

At Yahoo, I worked as a **SEM analyst** providing account management support to Advertisers. The role primarily included:

- Working with the Account managers and Account Operation Specialists in USA and Canada and providing them with Account Management support.
- Creating, Uploading and maintaining Advertiser Campaigns and various Search Ad formats.
- Finding Account Optimization opportunities to increase advertiser spend and improve account performance
- Quarterly Performance review and competitive insight decks for clients.

Education

MBA, PESIT

August 2012 - June 2014

B-Tech, VTU

August 2007 - Dec 2011